{
    "subject": "resource/Lionel_Messi",
    "predicate": "ontology/team",
    "object": "resource/Argentina_national_under-23_football_team",
    "human_readable": "Lionel Messi plays for Argentina national under-23 football team.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.8216114044189453,
            "question": "For which national team does Lionel Messi play?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8203245997428894,
            "question": "Is Lionel Messi part of the senior Argentine national team?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7840259671211243,
            "question": "In what age group does Lionel Messi play for Argentina?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6478415727615356,
            "question": "What sport does Lionel Messi play?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6242907047271729,
            "question": "What position does Lionel Messi typically play?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5244588255882263,
            "question": "Has Lionel Messi won any major tournaments with Argentina?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4171205163002014,
            "question": "What is Lionel Messi's nationality?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3188278377056122,
            "question": "Which club did Lionel Messi play for before joining Inter Miami CF?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3050575852394104,
            "question": "Is Lionel Messi considered one of the greatest football players of all time?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.24767355620861053,
            "question": "What are some of Lionel Messi's most notable achievements in his career?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Lionel Messi plays for Argentina national under-23 football team.",
            "html": "dbpedia_5754_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Is Lionel Messi considered one of the greatest football players of all time?",
            "html": "dbpedia_5754_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Which club did Lionel Messi play for before joining Inter Miami CF?",
            "html": "dbpedia_5754_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is Lionel Messi's nationality?",
            "html": "dbpedia_5754_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5754_138.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5754_163.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5754_18.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5754_29.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5754_60.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5754_62.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5754_74.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5754_78.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5754_87.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5754_90.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'no'}\n``` \n\n\n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "Based on the provided context information, I can evaluate the query \"Lionel Messi plays for Argentina national under-23 football team.\"\n\nHere is the result in JSON format:\n\n```\n{\n  \"output\": \"no\"\n}\n```\n\nExplanation:\nThe document with file_path \"/Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_5754/re-ranker-msmarco/83.txt\" mentions that Javier Mascherano, head coach of Argentina Under-23s, invited Lionel Messi to join his squad. However, it does not explicitly state that Messi accepted the invitation or is a part of the under-23 team. It only mentions that they share a close relationship and have played together for Barcelona and the Argentina senior side. Therefore, based on this information, we cannot confirm that Lionel Messi plays for the Argentina national under-23 football team."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents mention that Javier Mascherano, the head coach of the Argentina Under-23s, invited Lionel Messi to join his squad. This indicates that Lionel Messi is associated with the Argentina national under-23 football team, supporting the statement that he plays for this team."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": " {\n      \"output\": \"no\"\n   }"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 0,
    "actual_decision": 0,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "More Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {
        "qwen2.5": {
            "reason": "The context information mentions Javier Mascherano inviting Lionel Messi to join the Argentina Under-23s squad for the Olympics, but it does not state that Messi plays for this team. It only suggests a possible future involvement if he chooses to accept the invitation.",
            "category": 1
        }
    }
}